RG 009:007, Indian Litigation Files
Connecticut State Library
- Series 10. National Archives Microfilm, 1722-1906; bulk 1800-1870
  - Territorial Papers of the U.S. Senate, 1789-1873 National Archives film series M-200, [7 films of a 20 roll series]
    - Minnesota, 1847-1860 (Box 23, Folder 200-14)
    - New Mexico, 1840-1854 (Box 23, Folder 200-14)
    - Miscellaneous papers and papers relating to Territorial affairs in general, 1806-1867 (Box 23, Folder 200-20)
  - Records of the Cherokee Indian Agency in Tennessee, 1801-1835 National Archives film series M-208, [3 films of a 14 roll series]
    - Correspondence and miscellaneous records, 1801-1802 (Box 23, Folder 208-1)
    - Correspondence and miscellaneous records, 1808-1809 (Box 23, Folder 208-4)
    - Agency letter books, 1822-1835 (Box 23, Folder 208-10)
    - Records of the Agent for the Department of War in Tennessee, 1800-1815 (Box 23, Folder 208-14)
    - Records of Joseph McMinn, Agent for Cherokee Removal, 1817-1821 (Box 23, Folder 208-14)
  - Reports to Congress from the Secretary of War, 1803-1870 National Archives film series M-220, [3 films of a 5 roll series]
    - Vols. 1 & 2, 1803 February 3-1829 January 20 (Box 23, Folder 220-1)
    - Vols. 3 & 4, 1829 January 14-1840 March 20 (Box 23, Folder 220-2)
    - Vols. 5 & 6, 1840 March 20-1851 March 1 (Box 23, Folder 220-3)
  - Letters Received by the Office of Indian Affairs, 1824-1881 National Archives film series M-234A, [1 film of a 200 roll series]
    - Cherokee Agency, East, 1834-1836 (Box 23, Folder 234-76)
  - Letters Received by the Office of Indian Affairs, 1824-1881 National Archives film series M-234B, [7 films of a 200 roll series]
    - Miscellaneous, 1824-1826 (Box 23, Folder 234-429)
    - Miscellaneous, 1827 (Box 23, Folder 234-430)
    - Miscellaneous, 1828 (Box 23, Folder 234-431)
    - Miscellaneous, 1829 (Box 23, Folder 234-432)
    - Miscellaneous, 1830 (Box 23, Folder 234-433)
    - Miscellaneous, 1831-1832 (Box 23, Folder 234-434)
    - Miscellaneous, 1833-1835 (Box 23, Folder 234-435)
  - Letters Received by the Office of Indian Affairs, 1824-1881 National Archives film series M-234E, [1 film of a 162 roll series]
    - Six Nations Agency, 1824-1834 (Box 23, Folder 234-832)
  - Papers of the Continental Congress, 1774-1789 National Archives film series M-247A, [4 films of a 200 roll series]
    - War Office and the Department of War, 1776-1788 (Box 23, Folder 247-34)
    - Indian Affairs and lands in the Western Territory, 1776-1788 (Box 23, Folder 247-37)
    - Estimates and Other Papers Relating to the Treasury, 1780-1788 (Box 23, Folder 247-156)
    - Letters and Papers of Bankers in Holland and Contracts for Loans, 1779-1790 (Box 23, Folder 247-156)
    - Register of Incidental Accounts, 1785-1789 (Box 23, Folder 247-156)
    - Copies of Indian Treaties, 1784-1786 (Box 23, Folder 247-194)
    - Copies of Ordinances of the Confederation Congress, 1781-1788 (Box 23, Folder 247-194)
    - Returns of Inhabitants of Various States, and Miscellaneous Papers, 1774-1786 (Box 23, Folder 247-194)
  - Miscellaneous Papers of the Continental Congress, 1774-1789 National Archives film series M-332, [1 film of a 10 roll series]
    - Papers relating to specific states and deeds of cession of western lands, with related documents, 1779-1802 (Box 23, Folder 332-7)
      Includes the engrossed proclamation of the Continental Congress naming commissioners to settle the land dispute between Pennsylvania and Connecticut, August 28, 1782; Deeds of cession of Western and other lands with related documents, pertaining to the States of Connecticut, Georgia, Massachusetts, New York, North Carolina, South Caroline, and Virginia, 1784 – 1802
  - Report Books of the Office of Indian Affairs, 1838-1885 National Archives film series M-348, [4 films of a 53 roll series]
    - Vol. 1, 1838 November 25-1840 March 21 (Box 23, Folder 348-1)
    - Vol. 2, 1840 March 21-1841 August 31 (Box 23, Folder 348-2)
    - Vol. 3, 1841 September 1-1843 August 17 (Box 23, Folder 348-3)
    - Vol. 4, 1843 August 18-1846 February 26 (Box 23, Folder 348-4)
  - Ratified Indian Treaties, 1722 – 1869, National Archives film series M-668, [6 films of a 16 roll series]
    - Treaties 1-30, 1772 August 14-1801 October 24 (Box 23, Folder 668-2)
    - Treaties 31-60, 1801 December 27-1814 July 22 (Box 23, Folder 668-3)
    - Treaties 61-95, 1814 August 9-1818 June 22 (Box 23, Folder 668-4)
    - Treaties 96-143, 1818 August 24-1825 November 7 (Box 23, Folder 668-5)
    - Treaties 144-170, 1826 January 24-1832 September 21 (Box 23, Folder 668-6)
    - Treaties 171-196, 1832 October 11-1834 December 17 (Box 23, Folder 668-7)
  - Letters Sent by the Department of Justice: General and Miscellaneous, 1818-1904 National Archives film series M-699, [3 films of a 81 roll series]
    - Vol. A1, 1818 January 17-1833 December 26 (Box 23, Folder 699-1)
    - Vol. A2, 1818 January 17-1858 July 14 (Box 23, Folder 699-2)
    - Vol. B1, 1834 January 15-1850 October 1 (Box 23, Folder 699-4)
  - Selected Classes of Letters Received by the Indian Division of the Office of the Secretary of the Interior, 1849-1880 National Archives film series M-825
    - Attorney General, 1852 August 30-1873 December 31 (Box 23, Folder 825-12)
  - Transcribed Reports and Communications Transmitted by the Executive Branch to the U.S. Senate, 1789-1819, and Transcribed Reports of Senate Committees, 1798-1817 National Archives film series M-1257, [4 films of a 4 roll series]
    - Transcribed Reports and Communications, 1789-1791 (Box 23, Folder 1257-1)
    - Transcribed Reports and Communications, 1793-1796 (Box 23, Folder 1257-2)
    - Transcribed Reports and Communications relating Chiefly to Claims, 1789-1814 (Box 23, Folder 1257-2)
    - Transcribed Reports and Communications, 1798-1819 (Box 23, Folder 1257-3)
    - Transcribed Reports of Senate Committees, 1798-1817 (Box 23, Folder 1257-3)
    - Transcribed Report of the Attorney General, 1796 (Box 23, Folder 1257-4)
    - Transcribed Report of the Treasurer of the United States, 1790-1791 (Box 23, Folder 1257-4)
  - Transcribed Reports of the Committees of the U.S. House of Representatives, 1789-1841 National Archives film series M-1267, [8 films of a 15 roll series]
    - Transcribed Reports of the Committee on the District of Columbia, 10th Congress, 1st session, through 27th Congress, 1st session, 1807-1833 (Box 23, Folder 1267-6)
    - Transcribed Reports of the Committee on Military Affairs, 14th Congress, 1st session, through 19th Congress, 2nd session, 1816-1827 (Box 23, Folder 1267-6)
    - Vol. 1, Transcribed Reports of the Committee on Ways and Means, 3rd Congress, 1st session, through 7th Congress, 2nd Session, 1794-1803 (Box 23, Folder 1267-9)
    - Vol. 2, Transcribed Reports of the Committee on Ways and Means, 8th Congress, 1st session, through 18th Congress, 2nd session, 1803-1825 (Box 23, Folder 1267-9)
    - Vol. 1, Transcribed Reports of Select Committees, 1st Congress, 1st session, through 4th Congress, 1st Session, 1789-1796 (Box 23, Folder 1267-10)
    - Vol. 2, Transcribed Reports of Select Committees, 4th Congress, 2nd session, through 6th Congress, 2nd Session, 1789-1796 (Box 23, Folder 1267-11)
    - Vol. 3, Transcribed Reports of Select Committees, 8th Congress, 2nd session, through 11th Congress, 3rd Session, 1801-1804 (Box 23, Folder 1267-12)
    - Vol. 4, Transcribed Reports of Select Committees, 8th Congress, 2nd session, through 11th Congress, 3rd Session, 1804-1811 (Box 23, Folder 1267-13)
    - Vol. 5, Transcribed Reports of Select Committees, 12th Congress, 1st session, through 14th Congress, 1st Session, 1811-1816 (Box 23, Folder 1267-14)
    - Vol. 6, Transcribed Reports of Select Committees, 14th Congress, 2nd session, through 15th Congress, 2nd Session, 1816-1819 (Box 24, Folder 1267-15)
  - Transcribed Reports and Communications Transmitted by the Executive Branch to the U.S. House of Representatives, 1789-1819 National Archives film series M-1268, [7 films of a 15 roll series]
    - A Record of the Reports of the Secretary of State, 1st Congress, 1st Session, through 5th Congress, 2nd Session, Volumes I-II, 1790-1798 (Box 24, Folder 1268-1)
    - A Record of the Reports of the Secretary of State, 5st Congress, 3rd Session, through 14th Congress, 1st Session, Volumes III-IV, 1798-1816 (Box 24, Folder 1268-2)
    - A Record of the Reports of the Secretary of War, 1st Congress, 2nd Session, through 2nd Congress, 2nd Session, Volumes I-II, 1790-1793 (Box 24, Folder 1268-11)
    - A Record of the Reports of the Secretary of War, 3rd Congress, 1st Session, through 13th Congress, 2nd Session, Volumes III-IV, 1793-1814 (Box 24, Folder 1268-12)
    - A Record of the Reports of the Secretary of War, 13th Congress, 2nd Session, through 15th Congress, 1st Session, Volume V, 1814-1818 (Box 24, Folder 1268-13)
    - Confidential Reports and other Communications from the Secretary of War, 3rd Congress, 1st Session, 1793, Volume IIA; Record of the Reports of the Secretary of the Navy of the United States, 5th Congress, 3rd Session through 12th Congress, 1st Session, Volume I, 1798-1812 (Box 24, Folder 1268-14)
    - Record of the Reports of the Secretary of the Navy of the United States, 1812-1820 (Box 24, Folder 1268-15)
    - Record of the Reports of the Attorney General of the Unites States, 1790-1818 (Box 24, Folder 1268-15)
  - Unbound Records of the U.S. Senate, 8th Congress 1803-1805 National Archives film series M-1403, [1 film of a 5 roll series]
    - Includes: Foreign Relations; Indian Relations; Records of Impeachment Proceedings; Records of the Office of the Secretary, 1803-1805 (Box 24, Folder 1403-5)
  - Unbound Records of the U.S. Senate, Fifth Congress, 1797-1799 National Archives film series M-1704, [5 films of a 5 roll series]
    - Records of Legislative Proceedings: Bills and Resolutions Originating in the Senate Bills and Resolutions Originating in the House and Considered in the Senate, 1797-1799 (Box 24, Folder 1704-1)
    - Committee Reports and Papers President’s Messages, 1797-1799 (Box 24, Folder 1704-2)
    - Reports and Communications Submitted to the Senate (SEN 5A-Fi) Petitions and Memorials, Resolutions of the State Legislatures, and Related Documen, 1797-1799 (Box 24, Folder 1704-3)
    - Other Records: Records of Executive Nominations Foreign Relations, 1797-1799 (Box 24, Folder 1704-4)
    - Indian Relations; Other Records; Records of Impeachment Proceedings; Impeachment of William Blount; Records of the Office of the Secretary; Letters and Papers, 1797-1799 (Box 24, Folder 1704-5)
  - Unbound Records of the U.S. House of Representatives Fifth Congress, 1797-1799
    - Records of Legislative Proceedings: Bills Originating in the House; Committee Reports and Papers; and Petitions and Memorials, Resolutions of State Legislatures, and Related Documents that were referred to Committee, 1797-1799 (Box 24, Folder 1705-1)
    - Records of Legislative Proceedings: Bills Originating in the House; Committee Reports and Papers; and Petitions and Memorials, Resolutions of State Legislatures, and Related Documents that were referred to Committee, 1797-1799 (Box 24, Folder 1705-1)
  - Letters from and Opinions of Attorney General, 1791-1811 (Box 24, Folder T326-1)
  - Opinions of the Attorney General
    - Volume A, 1817 November 17-1821 June 19 (Box 24, Folder T412-1)
    - Volume B, 1821 June 1-1826 June 6 (Box 24, Folder T412-2)
    - Volume C, 1826 June 24-1832 January 11 (Box 24, Folder T412-3)
  - Documents Relating to the Negotiation of Ratified and Unratified Treaties with Various Tribes of Indians, 1801-1869, Record Group 75, Records of the Bureau of Indian Affairs
    - Introduction and Ratified Treaties, 1801-1826 (Box 24, Folder T494-1)
    - Ratified Treaties, 1827-1832 (Box 24, Folder T494-2)
    - Ratified Treaties, 1833-1837 (Box 24, Folder T494-3)
  - Miscellaneous Records, E.113 & 116, Record Group 75 (Box 24, Folder F#46)
  - Records of the Bureau of Indian Affairs, Miscellaneous Records, Volume 1, pages 55-62 & 275-277; Volume 2, pages 88-92; Volume 3, pages 33-36. E113/11E3/11/35/1, 1836-1837 (Box 24, Folder 289)
  - Records of the Office of the Secretary of War Decisions, Orders, and Regulations, Volume 2, page 29, M/F 244-247 paper (Box 24, Folder F#358)
- Series 11. Miscellaneous Microfilm, circa 1797-1815, undated
  - Georgia Department of Archives and History, circa 1797-1815
    - Georgia. Executive Department, Incoming Correspondence File II, pre 1800 (Box 24, Folder 4-213)
    - Georgia. Executive Department, Incoming Correspondence File II, pre 1800 (Box 24, Folder 4-214)
    - Georgia. Executive Department, Incoming Correspondence File II, pre 1800 (Box 24, Folder 4-216)
    - Georgia. Executive Department, Incoming Correspondence File II, pre 1800 (Box 24, Folder 4-217)
    - Georgia. Executive Department, Incoming Correspondence File II, pre 1800 (Box 24, Folder 4-220)
    - "Letters of Benjamin Hawkins" compiled, copied, indexed...by Louise Caroline Frederick Hays, 1797-1815; 1 reel (Box 24, Folder 2947)
  - New York Historical Society, undated
    - Henry O'Reilly Collection - Papers Relating to Six Nations Selections from Volumes 6-15, undated; service copy, 1 reel (Box 24)
- Series 12. Removable Media, 2002
  RESTRICTED
  - Golden Hill - Bureau of Indian Affairs, Acknowledgment Criteria Charts a, c, d, e, f, & g, 2002 June 14; 1 - 3.5 in. floppy disk (Folder 1)
    This item is separated from these records. Contact State Archives staff for assistance.
  - Golden Hill - Bureau of Indian Affairs, Acknowledgment Criteria Charts b, 2002 June 14; 1 - 3.5 in. floppy disk (Folder 2)
- Series 13. Restricted, circa 1959-1994
  - Attorney General - Correspondence
    - Correspondence - Office of the Governor, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Attorney General - Subject Files
    - List of sources - final determination - Golden Hill Paugussett Tribe, undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Golden Hill - Legal Documents
    - Golden Hill Paugussett Tribe of Indians vs. Lowell P. Weicker, Jr. - privilege case law, circa 1959-1994, undated (Box 25, Folder 3)